[
	{
    	"id": "723",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which best describes an AWS VPC?",
      	"answers": [
        	"VPC is a virtual data center in the cloud",
        	"VPC is a logical link from your on premises data center to the AWS cloud",
        	"VPC is a network configuration that allows you to have high speed, low latency connectivity to the AWS cloud"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["VPC is a virtual data center in the cloud"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "724",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "The best description of an AWS VPC: lets you provision __________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"a logically isolated section of the AWS cloud where you can launch AWS resources that you define",
        	"a network of highly available virtual machines",
        	"a physical section of the AWS cloud where you can launch AWS resources that you define"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["a logically isolated section of the AWS cloud where you can launch AWS resources that you define"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "725",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      	"question": "In your AWS VPC you have control ovwer which of these?",
      	"answers": [
        	"selection of your own ip address range",
        	"creation of subnets",
        	"configuration of route tables and network gateways",
        	"selection of your own data center"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["selection of your own ip address range",
        	"creation of subnets",
        	"configuration of route tables and network gateways"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "726",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "IN your VPC, you should place your web servers in which?",
      	"answers": [
        	"public facing subnet that has access to the internet",
        	"private facing subnet with no internet access"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["public facing subnet that has access to the internet"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "727",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "IN your VPC, you should place your database and application servers in which?",
      	"answers": [
        	"public facing subnet that has access to the internet",
        	"private facing subnet with no internet access"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["private facing subnet with no internet access"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "728",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      	"question": "In your VPC, which of these can you use to control access to the EC2 instances in your VPC?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Security Groups",
        	"Network Access Control Lists",
        	"Bucket Policies",
        	"IAM Policy Groups"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Security Groups",
        	"Network Access Control Lists"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "729",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "How can you use VPC to create an extension of your corporate data center?",
      	"answers": [
        	"create a hardware VPN connection between your data center and your VPC",
        	"use a snowball edge to establish a connection between your VPC and your data center",
        	"create a direct connct line between your VPC and your data center",
        	"use VPC peering between your VPC and your corporatew data center"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["create a hardware VPN connection between your data center and your VPC"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "730",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "What do you use to connect your internet users to your public facing subnet in your VPC?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Internet Gateway",
        	"Virtual Private Gateway",
        	"Bastion Host",
        	"Network Address Translation Gateway"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Internet Gateway"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "731",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "What do you use to connect your VPN users to your public facing subnet in your VPC?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Internet Gateway",
        	"Virtual Private Gateway",
        	"Bastion Host",
        	"Network Address Translation Gateway"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Virtual Private Gateway"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "732",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In a VPC, security groups can't span subnets?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "733",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In a VPC, a subnet can live in more than one AZ?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "734",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these is not a valid VPC subnet range?",
      	"answers": [
        	"10.0.0.0 - 10.255.255.255 (10/8 prefix)",
        	"172.16.0.0 - 172.31.255.255 (172.16/12 prefix)",
        	"192.168.0.0 - 192.168.255.255 (192.168/16 prefix)",
        	"164.168.0.0 - 164.168.255.255 (164.168/16 prefix)"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["164.168.0.0 - 164.168.255.255 (164.168/16 prefix)"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "735",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In a VPC, what does the router use to decide which Network ACL to rout to?",
      	"answers": [
        	"the route table",
        	"the subnet group",
        	"the security group",
        	"the public subnet",
        	"the private subnet"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["the route table"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "736",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "There is a limit (5) of the number of VPCs you can create in a region?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false",
        	"true, but it's a soft limit (you can have AWS increase the limit)"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["true, but it's a soft limit (you can have AWS increase the limit)"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "737",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Within your VPC you can launch instances into a subnet of your own choosing?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["true"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "738",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Within your VPC you can't assign custom ip address ranges in each subnet?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "739",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Within your VPC you can't configure route tables between subnets?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "740",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "How many Internet Gateways can you connect to you VPC?",
      	"answers": [
        	"1",
        	"2",
        	"multiple"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["1"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "741",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "How are Internet Gateways made highly available?",
      	"answers": [
        	"they are spread across all AZs in your VPC's region",
        	"they aren't highly avaiulable",
        	"they are replicated to another region"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["they are spread across all AZs in your VPC's region"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "742",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "How can you create and deploy EC2 instances quickly within your account?",
      	"answers": [
        	"use the default VPC",
        	"you have to create a VPC before you can delpoy EC2 instances",
        	"deploy your EC2 instances in your on premises data center"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["use the default VPC"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "743",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "All subnets in the default VPC have ________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"a route to the internet",
        	"a option to be made private",
        	"unencrypted EBS volumes as the root volumes to their EC2 instances"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["a route to the internet"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "744",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "The default VPC can have private subnets?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "745",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In the default VPC, each EC2 instance has ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"both a public and a private ip address",
        	"only a public ip address",
        	"only a private ip address"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["both a public and a private ip address"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "746",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "What allows you to connect one VPC with another via a direct network route using private ip addresses?",
      	"answers": [
        	"VPC Peering",
        	"VPC Routing",
        	"VPC mirroring",
        	"VPC Replication"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["VPC Peering"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "747",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Whith VPC Peering, EC2 instances ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"behave as if they are on the same private network",
        	"behave as if they are on the same public network",
        	"behave as if they are on different private networks",
        	"behave as if they are on the different public networks"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["behave as if they are on the same private network"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "748",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      	"question": "Whith VPC Peering, you can peer VPCs with __________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"other VPCs in other AWS accounts",
        	"other VPCs in the same accoppunt",
        	"other VPCs in your corporate data center",
        	"other VPCs that are in a transitive configuration"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["other VPCs in other AWS accounts",
        	"other VPCs in the same accoppunt"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "749",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "VPC peering uses __________ or ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"a star configuration, a hub and spoke model",
        	"a transitive configuration, a daisy chanined model",
        	"a bus configuration, a push/pull model",
        	"a shotgun configuration, a radius model"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["a star configuration, a hub and spoke model"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "750",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these are not part of a VPC configuration?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Internet Gateways",
        	"Virtual Private Gateways",
        	"Route Tables",
        	"Network Access Control Lists",
        	"Subnets",
        	"Security Groups",
        	"Virtual Private Networks"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Virtual Private Networks"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "752",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "NACLs are _________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"stateful",
        	"stateless"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["stateless"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "753",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Security Groups are _________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"stateful",
        	"stateless"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["stateful"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "754",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "VPC",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "VPC Peering can be used in a transitive way (ie. if VPC-a peers with VPC-b and VPC-b peers with VPC-c, then VPC-a can peer with VPC-c?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	}
]

